http://www.rrauction.com/privacy.cfm

Search Current Auction
By:
New Bidder Registration
Forgot your password?
Current Auction
Ends December 17th
HIDE CATEGORIES
Steve Jobs & Apple (21)
Businessmen (1)
Scientists and Inventors (4)
Science and Technology (1)
All Auction Items (26)
Bidding
How Do I Bid?
What is BidTracker™?
New Bidder Registration
The 30-Minute Rule
Terms and Conditions
New to RR Auction?
RRAUCTION.COM PRIVACY POLICY
January 10, 2001 RRAUCTION.COM is committed to protecting consumer privacy online. We believe that greater protection of personal privacy on the web will not only protect consumers, but also increase consumer confidence and ultimately their participation in online activities. At RRAUCTION.COM we intend to give you as much control as possible over your personal information. The purpose of our policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you when you visit our site, how we may use that information, whether we disclose it to anyone, and the choices you have regarding our use of, and your ability to correct, the information. Our site may contain links to other web sites. We have no control over the privacy practices or the content of any of our business partners, advertisers, sponsors or other sites to which we provide links from our site. You should check the applicable privacy policy of the web site sponsor when linking to other web sites. I. Information Which We Collect We may request that you voluntarily supply us with personal information, including your e-mail address, postal address, home or work telephone number, credit card number (only if you choose to purchase a product online), for purposes such as correspondence, making a purchase, or participating in online
bidding or surveys. If you choose to give us personal information via the Internet that we or our business partners may need -- to correspond with you, process an order or provide you with a subscription, for example -- it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information.
Like many other commercial sites, our site may utilize a standard technology called a "cookie" to collect information about how our site is used. Cookies were designed to help a web site recognize a user's browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot retrieve any other data from your hard drive, pass on a computer virus, or capture your e-mail address. Our web sites may use cookies to enhance your visit. Cookies can securely store a user's password, personalize home pages, identify which parts of a site have been visited or keep track of selections, such as those selected in a "shopping cart." Our cookies may collect your domain name and track your selections through our web pages. We only use "cookies" to gather the information indicated in this policy and do not use cookies to gather personal identifying information about you without your consent.
II. Use of User Information We may perform statistical analyses of aggregate user behavior. This allows us to measure relative consumer interest in the various areas of our web sites for product development purposes. Any information we collect is used for its own internal purposes to improve the content of the web sites, to enhance users' experiences when visiting our site, to customize the content and/or layout of our pages, and to provide the services required by an individual user. We do not use personal identifying information for any reason that is not disclosed either in this Policy or at the time the information is requested. We never send e-mail to you unless you request a particular service, or consent to being contacted by e-mail. There are instances where you will have the opportunity to subscribe to an e-mail list that will send information about the site or our advertisers to your e-mail address, but this will be done only with your permission and consent. III. Disclosure to Third Parties We do not share personal identifying information with any third party without your permission. We disclose only in aggregate form our statistical analyses or demographics of users to third parties, such as advertisers or other business partners.
These privacy policies are effective as of January 10, 2002. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect.
IV. Opting-out At any time while assessing our site(s), any user while online may "opt-out" of further e-mail contact from us (while still allowing access to our site). For further information about opting-out, contact us at the e-mail address, postal address or telephone number stated above.
V. Use of Materials The right to download and store or output the materials in our site is granted for the user's personal use only, and materials may not be reproduced in any edited form. Any other reproduction, transmission, performance, display or editing of these materials by any means mechanical or electronic without the express written permission of us is strictly prohibited.
RR Auction Autograph Auction 5 Route 101A, Suite 5 Amherst NH 03031 www.rrauction.com
Home |
How to Bid |
Register |
Consign |
User Agreement |
Contact Us |
About Us
RRAuction Official Time: Dec 11 2020 12:53:46 AM
Thirty Minute Rule Begins at 7:00PM ET on Thursday, December 17, 2020 For The Current Auction (#598)
Phone:  Toll free at (800) 937-3880 or Internationally at +1 (603) 732-4280
Fax:      Toll free at (888) 790-2437 or Internationally at +1 (603) 732-4288
Our site looks & works best on current browsers; if you are experiencing difficulty, please visit our browser upgrade page.Technical Problem? Email our system administrator at: webmaster@rrauction.com
Copyright © 2002–2020 RR Auction,  View our Privacy Policy
